khmer.be 2017-07-12

# Khmer.be

**Effective date: July 29, 2016**

Welcome to Khmer.be(“Khmer.be”,”we”,”us” or “our”), we created Khmer.be to help you connect with your Khmer family and friends anywhere around the world. We provide a fun, easy and way to share your photo and video. Using our photo filters, you can make your photo even more beautiful with just a touch on the button. 

This privacy statement (“Privacy Statement”) applies to the treatment of personally identifiable information submitted by, or otherwise obtained from, you in connection with the associated application (“Application”, “Website”, “mobile app”, “Service”). The Application is provided by Khmer.be (and may be provided by Khmer.be on behalf of a Khmer.be licensor or partner (“Application Partner”). By using or otherwise accessing the Application, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Statement. 

###  WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DOES Khmer.be COLLECT? 

####  We collect the following types of information from our users: 

**Personal Information You Provide to Us:**  
We may receive and store any information you submit to the Application (or otherwise authorize us to obtain – such as, from (for example) your Facebook account). The types of personal information collected may include your full name, username, e-mail address, Facebook Id, Facebook profile photos, Facebook friends’ id and Facebook friends’ full name; these are currently the information necessary for us to provide the Application services. 

User Content (e.g, photos, videos, comments, stickers and other materials) that you post to the Application. 

**Personal Information Collected Automatically:**  
We receive and store certain types of usage related information whenever you interact with Application. For example, Khmer.be may automatically receive and record information regarding your computer’s IP address, browser information, Facebook user ID, Facebook Page fan status, and URLs accessed. Such information may be shared in aggregate (non-personally identifiable) form with our partners. 

**Analytics Information:** We use third-party analytic tools to help us collect traffics to our Application. The tool might collect information sent by your web browsers and mobile device, including, not limit to, the web pages you visit, and other information that might help us analyze and improve the Application. 

**Mobile Device Identifiers:**

  * When you use a mobile device like a tablet or phone to access our Service, we may access, collect, monitor, store on your device, and/or remotely store one or more "device identifiers." Device identifiers are small data files or similar data structures stored on or associated with your mobile device, which uniquely identify your mobile device. A device identifier may be data stored in connection with the device hardware, data stored in connection with the device's operating system or other software, or data sent to the device by Khmer.be. 
  * A device identifier may deliver information to us or to a third party partner about how you browse and use the Service and may help us or others provide reports or personalized content and ads. Some features of the Service may not function properly if use or availability of device identifiers is impaired or disabled.

**Metadata:**

  * Metadata is usually technical data that is associated with User Content. For example, Metadata can describe how, when and by whom a piece of User Content was collected and how that content is formatted.
  * Users can add or may have Metadata added to their User Content including a hashtag (e.g., to mark keywords when you post a photo), geotag (e.g., to mark your location to a photo), comments or other data. This makes your User Content more searchable by others and more interactive. If you geotag your photo or tag your photo using other's APIs then, your latitude and longitude will be stored with the photo and searchable (e.g., through a location or map feature) if your photo is made public by you in accordance with your privacy settings.

### HOW DOES Khmer.be USE THE INFORMATION IT COLLECTS?

Khmer.be uses the information described in this Privacy Statement (i) internally, to analyze, develop and improve its products and services, and (ii) as set forth below in the “Will Khmer.be Share any of the personal information it Collects” section below. 

### APPLICATION PARTNER TREATMENT OF PERSONAL INFORMATION.

Khmer.be may provide personal information to the applicable Application Partner. The Application Partner’s use of your personal information is subject to the Application Partner’s separate privacy policy – and not this Privacy Statement. The Application Partner’s privacy policy is linked to from within the Partner’s Facebook application. 

### WILL Khmer.be SHARE ANY OF THE PERSONAL INFORMATION IT RECEIVES?

Personal information about our users is an integral part of our business. We neither rent nor sell your personal information to anyone (with the exception of sharing your information with an applicable Application Partner – see the “Application Partner Treatment” section above). We share your personal information only as described below. 

**Application Partners:**  
We will share your personal information with an applicable Application Partner (see the “Application Partner Treatment” section above). 

**Agents:**  
We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Unless we tell you differently, Khmer.be’s agents do not have any right to use personal information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. You hereby consent to our sharing of personal information for the above purposes. Business Transfers: In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that are transferred. Moreover, if Khmer.be, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Khmer.be goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Khmer.be may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy. 

Protection of Khmer.be and Others: We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with the law; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Khmer.be, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. 

With Your Consent: Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your personal information may be shared with third parties, and will be able to prevent the sharing of this information. 

### CONDITIONS OF USE

If you decide to use or otherwise access the Application, your use/access and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Statement and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of Washington State law. 

### THIRD PARTY APPLICATIONS/WEBSITES

The Application may permit you to link to other applications or websites. Such third party applications/websites are not under Khmer.be’s control, and such links do not constitute an endorsement by Khmer.be of those other applications/websites or the services offered through them. The privacy and security practices of such third party application/websites linked to the Application are not covered by this Privacy Statement, and Khmer.be is not responsible for the privacy or security practices or the content of such websites. 

### WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION CAN I ACCESS?

Khmer.be allows you to access the following information about you for the purpose of viewing, and in certain situations, updating that information. This list may change in the event the Application changes. 

  * User full name from your Facebook profile
  * Username that you select when signing up.
  * Application specific data

### CAN CHILDREN USE THE APPLICATION?

Our site and the services available through Khmer.be are not intended for children under the age of 17. Khmer.be does not knowingly or specifically collect information about children under the age of 17 and believes that children of any age should get their parents’ consent before giving out any personal information. We encourage you to participate in your child’s web experience. 

### CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT

Khmer.be may amend this Privacy Statement from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Statement in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes in the way we use personal information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our Site or sending you an email. Users are bound by any changes to the Privacy Statement when he or she uses or otherwise accesses the Application after such changes have been first posted. 

### QUESTIONS OR CONCERNS

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy on our Website, please send us a detailed message at https://www.facebook.com/Khmer.be/. We will make every effort to resolve your concerns.
